Giovany Emanuel Dominguez Ponce

IT Engineer

rastherdev@gmail.com

4432138396

, 000

linkedin.com/in/rastherdev



I worked in the area of systems, responsible for the attention and technical support to health clinics in the Morelia jurisdiction. With more than 2 years of experience I participated in 2 software development rpyects in medium-sized companies. I have developed my professional career in the field of web development, information technology and technical support.

EDUCATION

O Ingeniería en tecnologías de la información y comunicaciones

TecNM Campus Pátzcuaro

08/2015 - 06/2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Engineer | Technical Support Specialist Medical Minds S.A.

06/2022 - 07/2023

Morelia, Michoacan

- Tasks
- Technical support and assistance 24/7.
- Testing and incident reporting.
- Database management and encryption.
- Remote server administration.
- Network management.
- Data analysis.

Contact: Leticia Bazan - 4432196300

Web Developer

Never Too Much Money

12/2021 - 05/2022 (Remote) Kansas, EUA

- Tasks
- Web platform development.
- Hosting server management.
- Update and publish on the advertising website.
- Provide remote support of the platform.

Contact: Scott Schwartz - scott@nevertoomuchmoney.net

Web Developer

CEMA Mexico S.C. 03/2021 - 08/2021

Morelia, Mich.

- Tasks
- Develop the electronic logbook module.
- Provide support and maintenance to computer equipment.
- Design content for digital marketing.
- Develop laboratory specimen processing algorithms.

Contact: Laura Guadalupe Yacuta - sistemas@cemamexico.com

HARD SKILLS



COURSES

Web development using Codeigniter 4 (04/2021 - 07/2021)

- Usage of MVC
- Graphic interface design using templates.
- SQL Management, transactions, events.
- CRUD Actions.

GIT + GitHub: A whole version control system from scratch (10/2021 - 01/2022)

- Understanding the solid foundation of GIT
- Using GitHub for Project Management

SQL from scratch: Your practical guide to PostgreSQL (02/2023 - 04/2023)

 Mastering Database Management and Security with Microsoft SQL Server

ACHIEVEMENTS

Hackerrank SQL (Basic) Certificate

Hackerrank SQL (Intermediate) Certificate

Hackkernk Python (Basic) Certificate

LANGUAGES

Spanish Competencia Nativa o Bilingüe Enalish

Competencia Profesional de Trabajo

SOFT SKILLS

Ambition | Teamwork

Productivity